Mrs. Akshada Ajgaonkar (Kudalkar)



Mobile: 0565059750

□ akshadaarun.ajgaonkar@gmail.com

Summary:

A Pharma Post Graduate professional having in-depth Insurance Industry experience of 5+ years. Having hands on experience and thorough knowledge of handling Inpatient(ER/IP/Elective), Outpatient and Pharmacy insurance patient claims .A Positive, high-energy, self motivated and an ambitious Insurance Professional.

Personality Traits / skills:

- Strong learning ability, accepting new challenges and ready to apply knowledge practically.
- Good communication skills.
- Fluent command on English
- Believe in teamwork and cooperation to achieve organization goals.
- Adaptability, focused, flexible
- Complete knowledge of MS Office, basic knowledge of computer hardware and software

Experience Details:

March 2019 till date: DR. SUAIMAN AL HABIB HOSPITAL, DUBAI- UAE

Position held- Insurance Coordinator (ER/IP/Elective/Extensions)

Responsibilities-

- 1. verifying and entering patient's insurance coverage information, including benefits
- 2. responsible for validating patient's billing information, selecting and completing the insurance coverage information for the patient in their quest to access medical care
- 3. Applying for extensions of patient's admission if requested by attending doctors.
- 3. duties include calling up private insurance companies where patients have accounts to verify and obtain information concerning insurance benefits accruing to them

- 4. updating and re-filing patient's claims, re-verifying patient's current insurance, and finding out if a patient's insurance benefit plan takes into consideration all selected products needed by the patient
- 5. Establish contact with the ordering physician's office or customer service department to resolve issues concerning missing vital information from patients scanned requisition record
- 6. Work cordially in a team and participate in meetings, sharing ideas and information
- 7. Ensure timely processing of benefit information and facilitating discharge of the patient

August 2015 to February 2019: ZULEKHA HOSPITALS, DUBAI- UAE Position held- Insurance Coordinator (IP/OP/Pharmacy)

Responsibilities-

- 1. verifying and entering patient's insurance coverage information, including benefits
- 2. responsible for validating patient's billing information, selecting and completing the insurance coverage information for the patient in their quest to access medical care
- 3. duties include calling up private insurance companies where patients have accounts to verify and obtain information concerning insurance benefits accruing to them
- 4. updating and re-filing patient's claims, re-verifying patient's current insurance, and finding out if a patient's insurance benefit plan takes into consideration all selected products needed by the patient
- 5. Establish contact with the ordering physician's office or customer service department to resolve issues concerning missing vital information from patients scanned requisition record
- 6. Work cordially in a team and participate in meetings, sharing ideas and information
- 7. Ensure timely processing of benefit information and seek assistance from management when necessary
- 8. Cash collection from Patients of co payment charges

December 2014 till July 2015: Sanofi India

Position held- Product Executive

Responsibilities- Product promotion, marketing activities planning and execution, activity in charge, medical information pass on to health care professionals and end users, organizing scientific meets, achieving company targets and goals

Academic Qualification:

Sr.	COURSE	YEAR OF PASSING	COLLEGE	UNIVERSITY
-----	--------	--------------------	---------	------------

No.				
1	M. Pharmacy 2 nd Year	2014	Sinhgad Institute of Pharmacy, Pune	Pune
2	M. Pharmacy 1 st Year	2013	Sinhgad Institute of Pharmacy, Pune.	Pune
3	B. Pharmacy	2012	PES's RAT College of Pharmacy,Goa.	Goa
4	H.S.C	2008	D.M.C. Goa	Goa State Board
5	S.S.C.	2006	St. Mary's Convent High school, Goa.	Goa State Board

Achievements:

- Promoted as Team Leader
- Best Poster presentation at OMICS International Conference 2012.
- Runner-up in elocution competition in National Pharmacy Week 2013.
- Diploma in Bharatanatyam.
- Republic day parade representative from Goa NCC cadet.
- West zone winner of dance show on Sahara GROOVES
- Qualified NCC A Certificate examination held in 2005 under the authority of ministry of defense,
 Government of India.

Research Project Title:

 Formulation and Development of intranasal in-situ Liposomal Gel for Parkinson's disease.

Poster Presentation:

- **Poster presentation** at 65th IPC Delhi, 20-23 December, 2013- Dimenhydrinate polacrilex chewing gum -a novel approach for the treatment of motion sickness.
- Poster presentation at OMICS International Conference Hyderabad, November 2012-Simultaneous estimation of Hydrochlorothiazide and Quinapril using UV, IR, HPLC method

"A New Era of packaging of Syrup", Simulation Competition at BRAVURA2014, at Sinhgad
 Karandak Vadgaon, Pune.

Seminar Attended:

- 65th Indian Pharmaceutical Congress at New Delhi, 20th- 23rd December, 2013.
- Frontiers in Formulation and Development at Allana College of Pharmacy, 22nd- 24th
 August, Pune 2013.
- Analytica Acta at OMIC's International conference held at Hyderabad, November 2012.

Personal Details:

Husband's Name : Mr. Ritam Kudalkar

■ DOB : October 7, 1990

Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Indian

Gender : Female

Language known : English, Marathi, Hindi, Kokani.

Hobbies : Dancing, Singing, Writing, Elocution, Traveling.

References:

1. Mr. Jagannath Zarekar

Centaur pharmaceuticals Pvt. Ltd.

Deputy General Manager,

Mob.No. 9326018750

Sales and Marketing,

Declaration:

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct to my knowledge and bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Place: Dubai

(Mrs. Akshada Ajgaonkar)